[
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: hello",
        "Antwort": "hallo"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: never",
        "Antwort": "nie"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: food",
        "Antwort": "essen"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: cat",
        "Antwort": "katze"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: food",
        "Antwort": "essen"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: dog",
        "Antwort": "hund"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: you",
        "Antwort": "du"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: you are",
        "Antwort": "du bist"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: phone",
        "Antwort": "telefon"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: file",
        "Antwort": "datei"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: picture",
        "Antwort": "bild"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: cats",
        "Antwort": "katzen"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: light",
        "Antwort": "licht"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: window",
        "Antwort": "fenster"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: easy",
        "Antwort": "leicht"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: nice",
        "Antwort": "sch√∂n"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: chair",
        "Antwort": "stuhl"
    },
    {
        "Level": "easy",
        "Frage": "translate: plant",
        "Antwort": "pflanze"
    }
]
